http://www.truthforlife.org/about/policies/

Now Playing
There is nothing currently playing
The listening queue will play items sequentially from the "Up Next" list below.
Up Next
There is nothing in your queue.
You can add media by tapping the “add to queue” icon located near the media player.
Clear Queue
Remove 0
Series:
Videos cannot be added to the listen queue at this time.
This item is no longer available.
Follow Christ
Where Do I Start?
0 items
in your cart.
Subtotal:
$0.00
View cart
Checkout
Your cart is empty.
Start shopping now...
SignIn
Sign in
Don't have an account yet?
Daily Devotional
Online Bible (ESV)
Bible Reading Plan
Where Do I Start?
×
Welcome! Sign in.
ESV Bible
Audio and Video Content (DVD’s, CD’s, MP3 CD’s, & Digital Downloads)
Contact and Profile Information
Some areas of our Site request or require contact and other information
Copyright Policy
Truth For Life distributes Alistair Begg’s teaching material. As a ministry, we desire to see the Word of God proclaimed through all means. Therefore, we are excited to partner with you to give you easy access to much of our content for your personal use and to share with your friends. We are able to make these resources available because of financial support from listeners. As you use and share our content, please abide by the following guidelines to help us ensure the quality of the materials being distributed.
ESV Bible
Scripture taken from The Holy Bible, English Standard Version. Copyright ©2001 by Crossway Bibles, a publishing ministry of Good News Publishers. Used by permission. All rights reserved. Text provided by the Crossway Bibles Web Service.
Audio and Video Content (DVD’s, CD’s, MP3 CD’s, & Digital Downloads)
You may duplicate and distribute copies of Alistair’s sermons without prior permission as long as you:
Do not alter or edit the content in any way
Do not charge for the material (even to recover your fee)
Make a label or print on a CD “Copyright [message year] by Truth For Life. Used with Permission. www.truthforlife.org 1-888-588-7884”
Do not include personal or organization contact information with the copy.
Do not reuse Truth For Life’s logo.
You are welcome to show DVDs or streaming video of Alistair preaching in group settings.
If you would like to include a link to an audio or video clip on your site, you may embed a link to the file on our site. You must include a link back to our site at www.truthforlife.org.
Your use of the Audio and Video Content constitutes to an agreement by you and Truth For Life to be bound by these policies. Your use of this Content is provided under an irrevocable, nonexclusive and royalty-free right to use such Content subject to these terms. Please be aware that while all of our Audio and Video Content is free to use for non-commercial purposes in accordance with these terms, depicted items in the Content, such as identifiable people, logos, brands, etc. (other than of Alistair Begg or Truth For Life) may require the consent of a third party or the license of these rights. We do not represent or warrant that such consents or licenses have been obtained and expressly disclaim any liability in this respect. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless us from and against any and all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorney fees, resulting from your use of such Content and any violation of these terms.
Print Content
To use an excerpt from one of Alistair’s books or articles, please identify the publisher and contact that company directly. Truth For Life can only grant permission for re-use on items that we have published.
Unfortunately, we cannot grant permission to reprint the Morning & Evening devotional. For permission to reuse this content, please contact Crossway Books directly.
Web Content
You may post written content from www.truthforlife.org on your website as long as you:
Do not edit the content in any way
Include a link to the original article and our homepage (www.truthforlife.org)
Provide the appropriate credit for the content: “Copyright Truth For Life. Used with Permission. www.truthforlife.org.”
If you would like to post a web banner for Truth For Life on your site or blog, please visit our promotional resources page. We have a number of banners we have created for this purpose.
Truth For Life and Alistair Begg reserve all copyright protections under applicable law. We reserve the right to revoke or modify these permissions at any time.
If you would like to use content from Alistair Begg or Truth For Life in a manner that is not specified above, please contact us separately with the details of your request.
Refund Policy
All refunds will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase within five (5) business days upon receipt of the returned merchandise.
Donor Privacy Policy
Truth For Life takes the privacy of our donors very seriously. Any information that is shared with us is treated confidentially. We never sell  or trade the names of any donors or listeners to other organizations, nor do we rent our mailing list to other organizations. No mailings will be sent on behalf of other organizations. All other donor requests related to mailing lists (either print or digital) will be fully honored.
Internet Privacy Policy
Truth For Life has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site located at the URL www.truthforlife.org and any related subdomains.
In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. Truth For Life reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our Site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.
Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of;
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the Site;
Who collects such information;
How such information is used;
With whom your information may be shared;
What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information;
What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control;
and, How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Truth For Life by sending an email to letters@truthforlife.org. Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.
What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information
The information that we collect relates directly to the action being completed. Depending on the action, we may collect your name, email address, email format preference (HTML vs. Text), address, interests, and similar information. For financial transactions such as donations or store purchases, we will need to collect your credit card number. We use customer information collected to send the requested information, complete the requested transaction, and present the most relevant information to our listeners based on their interests. We never sell, share or trade any of our customer information with other companies.
Any transaction that can be completed online may also be completed via phone or mail, should you have concerns about security. Please see our contact page for information on reaching our customer service team.
Contact and Profile Information
Truth For Life is the sole owner of the information collected on the website. This site does not collect personally identifying information about users except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. For example, we collect information from you in the following ways:
Some areas of our Site request or require contact and other information
During the registration process, we collect personal and other information such as your name, address, and email address.
Demographic, interest, and profile data (e.g. gender, what stations you listen to, etc.) may also be collected at our Site.
Security
All information provided to Truth For Life is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We are compliant with the strictest industry standards for credit card security and processing, and our team regularly evaluates our systems and processes for additional safeguards.
Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. To increase the security of your transactions, please protect your usernames and passwords, be sure to log-out of the site when completing your transaction, and use a secure Internet connection when completing a financial transaction.
Choice/OptOut
Truth For Life provides users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. Truth For Life gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications:
You can email us at letters@truthforlife.org.
You can click on the "Unsubscribe" link included at the bottom of your email and follow the instructions on the web page. You may choose to opt-out of particular email newsletters or all email communication from Truth For Life.
Surveys
We may conduct occasional online surveys via our website or via an email newsletter. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate.
Contacting Truth For Life: If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us online or write us at:
P.O. Box 398000 Cleveland, OH 44139-8000
Tax Deductions
Your donation is tax deductible to the extent allowed by IRS Sec. 501(c)(3) regulations
Shipping policy
Standard shipping to the United States
United States Postal Service is our standard in shipping method in the United States. Barring complications, your order will be processed and shipped from our fulfillment office in Cleveland, OH within 1-2 business days of purchase. You should expect to receive your order within 7-10 business days.
In Ohio: Shipping and handling fees for orders purchased or shipped in Ohio are subject to 6.5% sales tax
Expedited shipping within the United States
UPS is our primary method for expedited shipping within the United States. Please call 888.588.7884 for expedited shipping service, weekdays, 8:00 am – 5:00 pm (ET). Orders placed by 1:00 pm (ET) are guaranteed to arrive in two business days.
International Shipping
International orders will be shipped using United States Postal Service. Any duty charges assessed in shipment will be the responsibility of the purchaser. Your order will be processed and shipped from our fulfillment office in Cleveland, OH within 1-2 business days of being placed.
Please note: It is the responsibility of the person placing the order to provide a correct address, deliverable by USPS for standard shipments or UPS for expedited shipments. If given an incorrect address (no apartment number or building number) by purchaser and product is returned to Truth For Life, the purchaser may be responsible for the loss of the product as well as shipping and handling costs. Shipping cost is non-refundable for unclaimed, undeliverable, or returned packages, unless we made a mistake in processing.
Whistleblower Policy
Truth For Life is committed to operating in furtherance of its tax-exempt purposes and in compliance with all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including those concerning accounting and auditing, and prohibits fraudulent practices by any of its board members, officers, employees, or volunteers. This policy outlines a procedure for employees and volunteers to report actions that an employee or volunteer reasonably believes violates a law, or regulation or that constitutes fraudulent accounting or other practices. This policy applies to any matter which is related to Truth For Life's business and does not relate to private acts of an individual not connected to the business of Truth For Life.
If an employee or volunteer has a reasonable belief that an employee, volunteer or Truth For Life has engaged in any action that violates any applicable law, or regulation, including those concerning accounting and auditing, or constitutes a fraudulent practice, the employee or volunteer is expected to immediately report such information to Alistair Begg or Robert H. Butts. If the employee or volunteer does not feel comfortable reporting the information to either of the above, he or she is expected to report the information to any board member.
All reports will be followed up promptly, and an investigation conducted. In conducting its investigations, Truth For Life will strive to keep the identity of the complaining individual as confidential as possible, while conducting an adequate review and investigation.
Truth For Life will not retaliate against an employee or volunteer in the terms and conditions of employment because that employee or volunteer: (a) reports to a supervisor, to the executive director, the Board of Directors or to a federal, state or local agency what the employee believes in good faith to be a violation of the law; or (b) participates in good faith in any resulting investigation or proceeding, or (c) exercises his or her rights under any state or federal law(s) or regulation(s) to pursue a claim or take legal action to protect the employee's rights.
Truth For Life may take disciplinary action (up to and including termination) against an employee or volunteer who in management's assessment has engaged in retaliatory conduct in violation of this policy.
In addition, Truth For Life will not, with the intent to retaliate, take any action harmful to any employee or volunteer who has provided to law enforcement personnel or a court truthful information relating to the commission or possible commission by Truth For Life or any of its employees or volunteers of a violation of any applicable law or regulation.
Supervisors will be trained on this policy and Truth For Life's prohibition against retaliation in accordance with this policy.
Conflict of Interest Policy
Every member shall avoid conflicts of interest. Transactions with related parties may be undertaken only if all of the following are observed: 1) a material transaction is fully disclosed in the audited financial statements of the member; 2) the related party is excluded from the discussion and approval of such transaction; 3) a competitive bid or comparable valuation exists; and 4) the member's board has acted upon and demonstrated that the transaction is in the best interest of the member.
About
Our Mission
What We Believe
The Gospel
About Alistair Begg
FAQs
App FAQs
Ministry FAQs
Home
Need Help?
Radio Station Finder
Welcome
Our Mission
FAQs
Alistair Begg
Follow Christ
Where Do I Start?
Our Resources
Blog
Sermon Archive
Series Archive
Topics
Devotionals
Add Devotional to Your Website
Bible
Insights Delivered to Your Inbox
Truth For Life is the teaching ministry of Alistair Begg and is committed to teaching the Bible with clarity and relevance so that unbelievers will be converted, believers will be established, and local churches will be strengthened.
Truth For Life is a qualified 501(c)(3) tax-exempt organization.
© 1994 - 2020 Truth For Life. All Rights Reserved.
Policies
|
Site Map
Truth For Life
